Muhammad Yekini



muhammadnurudeen@rocketmail.com



08164555012



linkedin.com/in/muhammad-yekini-90ba8bab

Summary

Web Mobile Specialist that writes well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development

Create website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS/BootStrap and JavaScript for interactivity. practices Integrating data from various back-end services like Node.js, Django and databases including MySQL.

Experience



Freelance Web Developer

Fiverr

Jan 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month +)

Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web Applications with HTML, CSS, JavaScript(Angular), Python and Django.

Provided front-end website development using HTNL/CSS, Bootstrap and other frameworks Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to generate project results and meet deadlines and organizational expectations.

Applied latest emerging technology, software and project application trends to update and maintain site applicability.



Data Entry Assistant (Planning & Budget Monitoring Department)

Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation

Oct 2018 - Dec 2018 (3 months)

Preparing and sorting documents for data entry

Entering data into database software and checking to ensure the accuracy of the data

Resolving discrepancies in information and obtaining further information for incomplete documents

Creating data backups as part of a contingency plan

Responding to information requests from authorised members

Education



Federal University of Technology Minna

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Mathematics and Computer Science Oct 2014 - Oct 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Health, Safety & Environmental Induction Course - Nigerian National Petroleum

Corporation

2018/927



Industrial Training (SIWES) - Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation

KRPC/R&R SIWES/80181078



Certificate of National Service - National Youth Service Corps

A 004633137

Skills

HTML5 • css3 • JavaScript • jQuery • Node.js • AngularJS • Python (Programming Language) • Django • TypeScript • SASS